Hey, Jerry, congrats on joining the
Colts.
Throughout your career,
one, what does it feel like to get
another contract in the NFL?
Congratulations on that. And then number
two, why was the Colts the best fit for
this chapter of your career?
Thanks. Yeah, no, it's great. It's
always a blessing to to be able to play
NFL football. You know, I still love
this game. I'm still having fun doing
it.
And it's great to have, you know, teams
and the organizations that are that that
that believe in me. And I'm excited to
go out and then
do my thing. And
you know, these coaches, this this
organization,
you know, it was it was a great fit for
me. You know, I
know coach Lou and um
coach Habbs and they've they've been,
you know, very
very good to me. And you know, they've
shown me, you know, what is to expect.
And you know, Shane I've known for a
while as well.
Coach Steichen. And so I'm excited to to
to move forward.
Joel.
You mentioned you knew Lou and and
Marion. What what Where's that What's
that relationship from? So, this was the
combine, I think.
Coach Habbs was in
um
I want to say Miami. And you know, it's
a small world, this NFL stuff. And so
you know, connections made are are
are usually remembered.
And Shane from the Chargers
long ago, obviously.
Anyone else?
Steven.
Hey, Jerry.
There we go. Sorry.
So, how does your your style maybe
fit or or not, you know, with with the
the scheme that's called to play?
Just how do you see yourself fitting in
just, you know, in terms of the
personality of your game?
For sure. Yeah, I know. I think
you know, being able to to play
aggressive, you know, stop the run, and
pass rush, and
quick [clears throat] identification of
schemes, and then knowing what the
offense is doing. These are all things
I'm you know, made a career doing. And
so you know, and they fit in any scheme.
And I think especially this one with the
way that, you know, Habbs and coach Lou
has us playing.
All right, cool. Thanks.
Joel.
Um
you know, what what do you think from a
veteran perspective,
you know,
what do you think you've you've kind of
learned over the years
um that sticks out about just the way
you play?
Sure. Yeah, I've you know, I've been
doing this a long time. I've I've been
on good teams. I've been on bad teams.
You know, I've seen good leadership.
I've seen bad leadership. And so
you know, taking everything you can from
your experience
and to try to replicate the good stuff.
And I think, you know, being having done
this for a while, it's important to um
to
to to bring that experience and share
what you've seen, what you've learned
with the team to try to try to make us
better. And that's [clears throat]
that's why I'm here.
All right, if no one has anything
further, that'll be it.
>> Hey, I got I got I got one more if you
don't mind. Sorry.
Jerry, looks and Sorry, I apologize. I
didn't get a chance to look this up just
yet. But when you were throughout your
career, you played all over the
defensive line. So, can can you just
give us I guess a rundown of what like I
guess what skills you think you excel at
the most? Like do you think you're more
of like a three-tech guy?
You know, more Can you slide out to the
outside? Like what do you view as like
your
>> Yeah, I know. I mean, I played nose last
year. You know, I played three-technique
throughout my whole career. I played on
the edge,
you know, five, six. I It's It's all
defensive line. And I think you know, I
can I can, you know, do whatever I can
to help us win, you know, make plays,
like be aggressive, and and and and have
fun with it.